Contact

vorago01@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jozsef-balib66164215 (LinkedIn) fenrir-codes.github.io/Datatekniker (Personal)

Top Skills

Technical Support Hardware Support Computer Hardware

Certifications

Learning C#

C# Object-Oriented Programming Tips and Tricks

Introduction to C# with Unity

Jozsef Bali

Student as Data technician specializing in programming.

Copenhagen, Capital Region, Denmark

Summary

I am 39 years old, with a lot of life experience. During my journey, I tried almost all kinds of work. I am currently doing what I have always wanted to do, I am studying what I have always been interested in, and I really want to find a place to practice. Currently i am working in Unity.

Experience

TEC - Technical Education Copenhagen Student October 2019 - Present (3 years 5 months) Denmark

Sjælandsk rengøring Cleaning Specialist August 2013 - May 2020 (6 years 10 months) Denmark

Sodexo Cleaning Assistant March 2015 - March 2017 (2 years 1 month) Denmark

GartnerJens Møller Employee June 2009 - March 2011 (1 year 10 months) Næstved, Zealand, Denmark

Vogel&Noot Austria Technician October 2004 - December 2007 (3 years 3 months) Austria

Worked on the technical department in the factory. Metalworking. Building sunroof panels, radiators, heating elements, etc...

Gartenbau Sattler GmbH Worker May 2002 - August 2004 (2 years 4 months) Austria

2F Computer science Student May 2000 - May 2002 (2 years 1 month) Győr-Moson-Sopron, Hungary

Education

Technical education Copenhagen

Datatekniker, Computer Programming · (2019 - 2024)

Technical Education Copenhagen Electrician · (August 2018 - January 2019)

2F Computer science Computer Science · (May 2000 - May 2002)